<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought it at 32500. It was a good price for me. It was cheap as compared to the price of the stores. After some hours the price dropped to 31500. I hope I had bought it at 31500.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good camera value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent camera and got for a best ever price of Rs.21k... But if you had used Nikon before you might feel little inconvenient with the settings of the camera especially with the lenses as the zoom rotation is reverse motion. So I had missed some beautiful clicks die to time mismatch. Still I believe I'll be comfortable handling it over a period of time...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The delivery is the worst part of my experience... I didn't get the consignment on the committed date. I had waited more than 10 days to receive my camera. Not only this, even my other purchases are not delivered on time...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;BOTTOM LINE : Best Entry Level Camera for noobs :D&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No words to describe !&lt;br&gt;This is my first DSLR Camera and I am very lucky to have this beast ! Its really worth a buy for price I got which was 25K :D&lt;br&gt;Both the lenses are awesome for capturing the images! build quality is as superior as canon always offer!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the Sample Images Clicked by me :&lt;br&gt;https://flic.kr/ps/2VfzXD&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good deal.... best camera&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best available deal and the best camera available at this price. Mind it, THE BEST at this price.&lt;br&gt;I would recommend this to all who are not pursuing photography as profession but still likes photography and dream to own a DSLR, this fulfills all the requirements and price is unbeatable. I got this for 20,990. keep watching this space for good deals.Really good product very satisfied however delivery is pathetic. The ARAMAX courier service could not track my shipment after 17 days of making payment. I had to collect my shipment once I escalated the matter after 17 days&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome product go for it.........!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome product with offer........... Yes my doubts got cleared i got my warranty for 2years, i spoke with one of the sales person from canon said they will register my warranty details and update, and before they register amazon already had it for 2yrs, so canon will again register with customers name as per the purchase date &amp;amp; will give you whole 2yrs warranty.&lt;br&gt;Apart from the warranty product came with good condition and perfect packing.&lt;br&gt;Now about the cam Canon EOS 1200D would be great for people with basic skill set in photography and ofcourse works fine too.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent product  &amp;amp; ,Profitable.....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased this item @ 23849( Ordering time price is Rs-25099-Sbi Debit card less 10 percentage, but Maximum less Rs-1250),Camera Body + 18-55 lens,55-250 lens +battery +charger+8 GB card+Carry case Special Season gift (from Canon) 5000 mah Power Bank(for mobile recharging)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Totally Amazon  provide grand profit to customers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for Amazon .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Review&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent clarity,User friendly,Thailand made Quality Product,Pictures are very colorful,.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop your comparison and purchase it !...........Good Product.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Camera&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am an amateur user to this DSLR league... I have been using my brother-in-law's 1100D and was always wanting to buy one... I was completely fed up with point n shoot &amp;amp; mobile cams... Amazon gave an amazing deal worth every rupee spent.. Got the cam a week before my HK trip and took a lot of pics.. It would not be appropriate for me to provide a detailed technical review as there are so much available... But trust me this is the best camera for this budget... Clicked few photos of food, people, moving train, ferries, birds, buildings, sky, rain and it looks damn good...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The camera quality is good. Although&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The camera quality is good.&lt;br&gt;Although, I'm still awaiting response to issue which I raised. As per the order details, I was to get power bank free.&lt;br&gt;I'm still waiting for the same.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best DSLR by canon for beginner and mid range photo crazy people.... :-)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After lot of research and consulting professional photographer, i ordered Canon 1200D dual lense pack.&lt;br&gt;i took almost two months to decide,&lt;br&gt;Canon is the top most in camera..the quality it provides is amazing.&lt;br&gt;other camera makers are providing many features, but if u want quality, go for canon.&lt;br&gt;i'm sure our first priority is quality and after that other things....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Package contains&lt;br&gt;1) Canon 1200D body&lt;br&gt;2) 18 55mm lens&lt;br&gt;3) 55-250 Lens&lt;br&gt;4) battery and charger&lt;br&gt;5) 5200mAh power Bank (digitek)&lt;br&gt;6) 2 years warranty&lt;br&gt;7) VAT invoice&lt;br&gt;8) Canon Camera Belt&lt;br&gt;9) Memory Card 8 Gb&lt;br&gt;these are the main things which a customer want&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the product was nicely packed and delivered in nice condition.&lt;br&gt;i tried with 18-55mm lens. quality is very good.&lt;br&gt;still going through the features.&lt;br&gt;this camera got tons of features, but i need to discover all.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;registered this camera on canon website and i got 2 years warranty.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Warranty issues&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is fine no issues ....but the canon website is showing that the product does not qualify for the 2nd year warranty ...if anyone could help me with that ....that would be great&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews></item></items>